<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blogs on chungman.kim</title><link>https://chungman.kim/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blogs on chungman.kim</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 17:48:30 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://chungman.kim/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Serving Assets to My Website Part 1</title><link>https://chungman.kim/2020/05/serving-assets-to-my-website-part-1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 May 2020 17:48:30 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://chungman.kim/2020/05/serving-assets-to-my-website-part-1/</guid><description>Serving assets, such as images and documents, to be accessible to end users is essential to a modern web experience. As for what I have in mind with this blog, I want to visually capture steps that I took to help jog my memory of what I did or learned.
Setting this up took me 30 minutes the first time. The steps are split into a series of posts to keep the posts short and organized.</description></item><item><title>Finding Purpose for Blogging</title><link>https://chungman.kim/2020/05/finding-purpose-for-blogging/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2020 22:01:38 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://chungman.kim/2020/05/finding-purpose-for-blogging/</guid><description>update I&amp;rsquo;ve taken my focus away from blogging to dedicate my time and energy on other efforts. Since my last post, a few noteworthy happenings came about. I switched jobs from Realogy (formerly known as ZapLabs) to Duetto, got my second AWS Certification, and heavily invested into learning Dart &amp;amp; Flutter to name a few. As exciting as each moment was, retaining and recalling everything that I&amp;rsquo;ve learned has been challenging.</description></item><item><title>Start</title><link>https://chungman.kim/2020/01/start/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 14:44:36 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://chungman.kim/2020/01/start/</guid><description>At this point, I&amp;rsquo;ve probably drafted and redrafted my first post more times than my hands and toes can count. Who knew that starting a blog could be both an exciting and uncomfortable experience? With that said, I&amp;rsquo;m looking forward to seeing what would become of this new endeavor. This introduction is for me and all those who are new to blogging.
Good luck.</description></item></channel></rss>